hello everyone this is Rahul zakara from
sherka welcome back to exciting 3
actionable stock updates 3 basically
means right sector right quality and
right Valu Vision these are our
investment
ideas today we have an update on icsa
Lombard our analyst maintains buy rating
on IC Lombard with a price target of
rupes 2200 IC lomard reported healthy
performance in quarter 1 mainly led by
Healthy Growth in premium and higher
investment income management is
confident about further Improvement in
Combined ratios by the end of fi25
thereby improving profitability we
remain optimistic about the company's
plan to grow in a calibrated manner we
expect the company to deliver Roe of 18
to 20% over the medium term at the
current market price the stock trades at
35.7 time fi25 and 30 * fi 26 estimated
EPS the stock has outperformed the
broader indexes in last 12
months next we have an update on Nam
India our analyst maintains buy rating
on Nam India with a price target of
rupes 750 Nam India reported yet another
strong quarter led by boyant Capital
Market flows it has been witnessing
strong growth across segments leading to
strong market gains on the back of
buyant markets
also its Equity Fund have been
delivering better performance in the
past years versus peers which is driving
improvement in net inflows impact of
lower Equity yields on core revenue is
expected to be broadly managed by higher
growth in AUM we expect npon to deliver
better than industry AUM growth at the
current market price the stock currently
trades at 30.8 times at SEI 25 and 27.6
times it's fi 26 earnings EPS estimates
the stock is out performed the broader
indexes in last 12
months investment and securities Market
are subject to Market risks read all the
related documents carefully before
investing